好了 乔希
All right, Josh.
该走了
Time to go.
再等五分钟
Five more minutes.
不 我数到3
No. I'm counting to 3,
再不走我要生气了
and then I'm going to get mad.
五分钟
Five more minutes!
1…
2…
2.5…
好啦
Come on.
晚饭想吃什么？
What do you want for dinner?
中国菜
Chinese.
你昨晚才吃过中国菜
You had Chinese last night.
我每天都得吃中国菜
I have to eat it every day.
为什么？
Why?
我要成为功夫大师
Be a kung fu master.
好吧 秀几招 小成龙
Well, show me your moves, Jackie Chan.
今晚的比赛你准备好了吗？
You ready for your tournament tonight?
是的 我要打到他血流不止
Yeah. I'm going to make him bleed.
我要让他哭着求饶
I'm going to make him cry.
我要打得他哭着回家找妈妈
I'm going to make him run home to his mama.
- 打谁？- 迈克尔 我讨厌他
- Who? - Michael. I hate him.
他 好像 是你的朋友
He's, like, your friend.
再也不是了
Not anymore.
为什么不是？
Why not?
因为他老是数落别人
Because he picks on people.
他也数落你？
Does he pick on you?
有时候吧
Sometimes.
我要跟他妈妈谈谈这件事
I'm going to talk to his mother about that.
不要 妈妈
No! Mom!
救命啊
Help!
《蝴蝶效应3： 启示》
把灯打开
Turn on the lights.
记下来
Write this down.
下午7点12分
7:12 p.m.
你还好吧？
You okay?
嗯
Yeah.
你看到了什么？
So what did you see?
你不会想知道的
You don't want to know.
不 我想知道 你觉得我这么做事为了什么好处吗？
Yes, I do. You think I do this for the great benefits package?
珍娜 别忘了今天你还有个约会
Jenna, don't forget your shrink appointment today.
我可不想听到你又换到另一个的消息
I don't want to hear you skipped another one.
喔 谢谢 珍娜 谢谢你的帮忙
Oh. Thanks, Jenna. Thanks for helping.
谢谢你在我穿梭时空的时候 保持我的大脑稳定
Thanks for keeping my brain stable while I jump through time.
不用谢 塞姆 我很乐意帮你
No problem, Sam. Glad I could help.
她会做的菜有… 熏肉卷
The things that she can cook… meatloaf.
我到家的时候 她穿着睡衣…
So I got home, and she's wearing her negligee…
烧到嘴巴时 那个效果还不错
You know it's good if you burn your mouth.
我们走
Let's go.
是那个人？
That's the guy?
那个就是通灵的人吗？
That's the psychic?
笑你的吧
Laugh all you want,
但这个通灵的人已经 把22个坏蛋关进监狱了
but that psychic's put 22 perps behind bars.
他把车开走了 但抢车不是他的目的
He took the car, but it's not what he was after.
是钱包？
The purse?
目标就是她 他是专门来杀她的
It was her. He was there to kill her.
那是谋杀… 买凶杀人
It was a hit… murder for hire.
塞姆 是谁买凶的呢？
Who hired him, Sam?
这是他手机的通话记录
It's in his cell phone records.
7点12分他打了一个电话
He made a phone call 12 after 7.
- 说嘛 他怎么知道这些的？- 不关你事
- Come on. How does he know this stuff? - Never mind.
去找她前夫的电话记录
Get the ex-husband's phone records.
看看他在那晚的7点12分有没有接到电话
See if he received a call at 7:12 that night.
因为孩子没受到伤害 我觉得前夫有嫌疑
I suspected the ex, the way that kid's left unharmed.
等一下 大侦探 呃…
Excuse me, Detective, uh…
尼古拉斯
Nicholas.
孩子不是没受伤
The kid wasn't unharmed.
他看到他妈妈被打死
He saw his mother bludgeoned to death.
估计我的支票在楼下呢
I assume my check is downstairs.
我不知道你是怎么知道这些的
I don't know how you know what you know,
但我知道你像巫师那样灵
but I know that you ain't no psychic.
来看看我是不是错了
Prove me wrong.
说说我妻子和我说的第一件事
Tell me the first thing my wife ever said to me.
真正的巫师会知道这些琐事的 塞姆
Real psychics know that kind of shit, Sam.
大侦探 我等你的电话
I look forward to your next call, Detective.
我们这个月和下个月的帐都结了
So this ought to settle us up for this month and next.
你看你 谁说你不是个窝心的小宝贝？
Look at you. Ain't you the sweetest thing?
你照顾你的姐姐的方式
The way you take care of your sister.
就像南瓜派那样甜蜜
About as sweet as pumpkin pie.
没错 你的确是这样
Yes, you are.
用你小嘴上的奶油
How sweet is pumpkin pie
做成的南瓜派该有多甜啊？
with some whipped cream on that sweet little ass of yours?
对 呃 那个
Yeah, uh, you know,
其实我要走了
I actually got to get going
因为我还要拿着些冰淇淋
because I got ice cream in the groceries.
我带你去认识我的侄女罗克珊
I need to introduce you to my niece Roxanne.
荣幸之至
I'd love to meet her.
好的 我把她的电话给你
Okay. I'll get her number for you.
好 好的
Yeah. Okay.
你在这别走 我马上就回来
You stay right there. I'll be right back.
好的
Right.
珍娜
Jenna.
没听到我敲门吗？
Didn't hear me knocking?
不知道是你在敲门
Didn't know it was you.
那你认为是谁？
Who'd you think it was?
盖世太保
Gestapo.
你在这开过窗吗？
You ever open up a window in here?
怎么了 没格调了？
What, and lose the ambiance?
你肯定不相信昨晚发生了什么
You're never gonna believe what happened last night.
说说看
Try me.
隔壁的卡罗维茨斯夫妇一直吵到很晚
The Kalowitzes next door were up late fighting.
真令人吃惊
Shocking.
来讲讲好的消息
Let me get to the good part.
她用了「离」字开头的绝招
She drops the D-bomb.
离婚？
Divorce?
看来3-B房间就快要空出来了
So it looks like Apartment 3-B might be opening up.
你可以住过来 我们就是邻居了
You could grab it. We could be neighbors.
没错 这样你就可以整夜偷听我的生活了
Yeah, then you could stay up late eavesdropping on me.
喔 是的 偷听你刺激的社交生活
Oh, yeah. Eavesdropping on your exciting social life.
这些东西会他妈的害死你的
Those things will fucking kill ya.
上帝保佑
Godspeed.
工作进展如何 警察巫师先生？
So how was work, Mr. Police Psychic?
找出来在公园杀害妈妈的是谁了吗？
We ever find out who killed Mommy in the park?
确定身份了？
Get an I. D?
没错 是前夫雇的杀手
Yeah. It was some gun the ex hired.
每次都是前夫
It's always the ex.
在佩吉和凯文
I should warn Peggy
离婚之前 我要去给她个警告
before she serves Kevin those divorce papers.
这样的话 你就不得不搬出公寓了
To do that, you'd actually have to leave your apartment.
抱歉 我在开玩笑
Sorry. That was just a joke.
不管怎样 我搬出公寓就是了
Anyway, I leave my apartment.
其实 我今天早晨去看了心理医生
In fact, I went out just this morning to see my psychoanalyst.
很好啊
Great.
不 说真的 珍娜 那… 那真的很好
No, seriously, Jenna. That's… That's great.
她说了什么？
What did she have to say?
她同意我的看法 对火灾中
She agreed with me that it's really unhealthy
发生的事情闭口不谈是不好的
that we never talk about what happened in the fire.
求求你 让我出去
Please! Let me out!
她说 我对那情况知道的越多
She said that the more I know about what happened,
我就越少受其困扰
the more I'll be free of it.
说真的 能聊聊那件事吗？
Seriously. Can we talk about it?
有什么好聊的？
What is there to talk about?
珍娜 你要为这付出代价吗 还是…
Jenna, were you gonna pay this, or…
警察说是瓦斯泄漏
The police said that it was a gas leak,
但你是从外面回来的
but you came in from outside.
我闻到烟味的
I smelled smoke.
我不知道烟是哪来的
I didn't know where it was coming from.
我以为是邻居家的
I thought it was the neighbor's house,
- 所以我出去看看 - 你还找到了梯子？
- so I went outside to look. - And you got a ladder?
- 是的 - 这完全说不通
- Yeah! - It just doesn't make any sense.
你怎么会有时间跑去棚子 还找到了梯子…
How did you have time to go to the shed and get a ladder…
你明白的 我不记得了 珍娜
You know, I don't remember, Jenna!
我不记得了
I don't remember!
我也不想记得 那时我只有15岁
I don't want to remember! I was 15 years old.
够了吗 珍娜？审问结束了吗？
Is that enough, Jenna? Is the interrogation over?
冰箱里有冰淇淋
Ice cream's in the freezer.
塞姆
Sam.
谢谢你帮我买零食
Thanks for the groceries.
你明天有什么事？
What are you doing tomorrow?
想过来吃晚饭吗？
You want to come over for dinner?
我可以做个煲
I could make a casserole.
好的 我明天过来
Yeah. I'll come by tomorrow.
一言为定？
Promise?
搞什么 我们还是三年级吗？
What are we, in the third grade?
一言为定？
Promise?
拉钩
Pinky swear.
好的
All right.
晚上睡个好觉 好吗？
Get some sleep tonight, okay?
找我什么事？
Can I help you?
你不认识我啦
You don't recognize me.
伊丽莎白布朗？
Elizabeth Brown?
丽贝卡的妹妹？
Rebecca's sister?
见到你还是很高兴的
Nice to see you, too.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
进来吧
Come on in.
地方不错
Nice place.
谢谢 是 还好啦
Thank you. Yes. It's all right.
这边 我帮你腾个座儿…
Here, let me clean off this seat for you…
不 不了 塞姆 别麻烦了
No. Don't. Sam, don't worry about it.
把这些垃圾扔出去
Get this crap out of the way.
什么风把你吹来了？
So what brings you to my part of town?
我来… 我来是为了那死刑
I came… I came back for the execution.
他们周五要处死罗尼
They're executing Lonnie on Friday.
注射死亡
Lethal injection.
罗尼… 罗尼弗莱内斯
Lonnie… Lonnie Flennons.
就是那个…
The guy that ki…
他们认为杀死丽贝卡的那个人
The guy they say killed Rebecca.
塞姆…
Sam…
看起来你不知道我在说什么
You act like you don't know what I'm talking about.
不 我… 我…
No, I… I…
不 我当然知道
Yeah. Of course.
我只是好久没想起丽贝卡了
I just hadn't thought about Rebecca in a long time,
就这样
that's all.
来一杯吗？
You want a drink?
这干净的
It's clean.
那么…
So…
你来这是干嘛的？
What are you doing here?
罗尼没有杀害我妹妹
Lonnie didn't kill my sister.
- 那你怎么知道？- 好吧…
- And how do you know that? - Well…
因为我在帮父母搬家时 发现了这本日记
Because I found this diary when I was helping my parents move.
丽贝卡写的很多都是你 塞姆
Rebecca wrote about you a lot, Sam.
关于她是多么爱你
About how much she loved you.
你还记得那时
Do you remember when
罗尼在审判时试图说服陪审团
Lonnie tried to convince the jury during the trial
你知道的 相信他们…
that, you know, they were…
在恋爱？
having a relationship?
- 你还记得吗？- 对 我记得
- Do you remember? - Yeah, I remember.
那是真的 塞姆
It was true, Sam.
丽贝卡对你不忠
Rebecca was cheating on you.
我知道这很伤人
I know this hurts.
看 1998年五月18号
Look. May 18th, 1998.
「有人一直在跟踪我
"Someone has been following me.
肯定不是塞姆
"It's definitely not Sam.
他还不知道罗尼 可我得告诉他
"He doesn't know about Lonnie, but I have to tell him.
我感觉如此愧疚
"I feel so guilty.
我不知道该怎么办「
I don't know what to do."
我把日记带给了警方
I took this diary to the cops.
他们说这…
They say it's…
不是确切证据 不能重新开庭
it's not sufficient evidence to reopen the case.
- 那么 要是他们这么说… - 然后
- Well, if that's what they say… - And then,
我跟你的朋友谈过 格伦侦探？
I talked to your friend. Detective Glenn?
塞姆…
Sam…
他告诉我你有办法了解
he told me that you have a way of knowing things
别人不知道的事情？
that nobody else knows?
他说… 说你能…
That… That you can…
调查犯罪
see into crime.
塞姆 我想要雇你
Sam, I want to hire you.
我有5000美元现金
I have $5, 000 in cash.
行不行？
Okay?
拿着
Here.
- 我不行 伊丽莎白 - 为什么？
- I can't, Elizabeth. - Why?
- 这很麻烦 我很抱歉 - 麻烦
- It's complicated. I'm sorry. - Complicated.
可是…
But…
杀害丽贝卡的凶手逍遥法外
the guy that killed Rebecca got away.
而罗尼弗莱内斯 一个无辜的人
And Lonnie Flennons, an innocent man,
一个她所爱的人
a man she loved,
将会死去
is going to die.
我倒希望能帮上忙
I wish I could help.
我真的 我…
I do. I…
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
塞姆…
Sam…
好吧
Okay.
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
算了吧
You forgot this.
留着吧
Keep it.
她会想要你留着的
She would have wanted you to have it.
那就 呃…
So, um…
跟我说说那个死去的女孩儿
Tell me about this dead girl.
你爱她吗？
Did you love her?
丽贝卡布朗
Rebecca Brown,
是我第一个为之倾心的女孩
first girl I ever fell for.
你之前从没想过回到过去？
You never thought about jumping back before?
想过一百次了 我只是…
Thought about it a hundred times. I just…
但你会更了解
But you'd know better.
塞姆 这是个严肃的事儿
Sam, this is serious shit.
有两大条规矩
There's two big rules.
你绝不能回去改变自己的过去
You never jump back to alter your own past.
还有你决不能在无人监管时回去
And you never jump unsupervised.
要是我只是回去而没人看到我呢？
What if I just go back and nobody sees me?
要是我…
If I…
要是我完全按你教的只是观察呢？
If I do exactly as you taught me and just observe?
得了吧 伙计 别自欺欺人了
Come on, man. Let's be honest with ourselves.
你真以为你能回去
Do you really think that you can go back
眼睁睁地看着你的女朋友被杀害
and watch your girlfriend get murdered,
- 却无动于衷吗？- 我曾看到许多人
- and not intervene? - I've seen dozens of people
就在我眼前被杀害
killed right before my eyes,
却什么也没做
and I haven't lifted a finger.
那 这可不一样 塞姆
Well, this is different, Sam.
你自己见识过 要是你…
You've seen for yourself what happens if you…
要是你打破规矩会发生什么事
if you break these rules.
你妹妹死于火灾
Your sister dies in a fire.
你回到过去 以为你能救她
You jump back, thinking you can save her.
而且你做到了
And you do.
可你没料到 取而代之
But what you didn't expect
你的父母会死去
was that your parents were gonna die instead.
你试图拯救一条人命 你却害死了两个
You try to save one life. You kill two.
在你了解规矩之前你要回去多少次？
How many times you gotta jump back before you know the rules?
15次？20次？知道我不会再那样就够了
15? 20? Enough to know I don't want to do it any more.
这就对了 你知道吗 你都快把脑袋弄糊涂了
Exactly. You know, you nearly fried your brain.
重复那么多次你会受不了的
You can't handle that many overlaps.
那样会让你发疯
It'll drive you crazy.
给我们再来一杯吧 甜心？
Can we get another round here, sweetheart?
省省吧 德伯格
Save it, Goldburg.
你大一物理给了我个「F」 还记得吗？
You gave me an "F" in freshman physics, remember?
你永远也不会让我忘了的
You're never gonna let me live it down.
你给小费 我可能会
You start tipping, I might.
不用找了
Keep the change.
大家都开心
Everybody's happy.
我知道这很难 伙计
I know it's hard, man.
可是不管什么原因
But for whatever reason,
你的女人丽贝卡必须死
your girl Rebecca had to die.
而我必须得忍受
And I've had to live with it.
不去拯救某人的生命
Not saving someone's life
并不意味着是杀害他们 塞姆
isn't the same thing as killing them, Sam.
不是
No.
但很接近
But it's close.
你在做好事 塞姆
You do a good thing, Sam.
你给人们带来很多了结
You bring a lot of closure to people.
除了我自己
Everybody but myself.
你不能继续活在过去了
You gotta stop living in the past.
你得把这个女孩抛在脑后
You gotta get this girl out of your mind.
她已经不在了
She's dead.
你再也见不到她了
You're never gonna see her again.
你要是想帮助这个可怜的死囚区杂种
And if you want to help this poor death-row bastard,
那你最好在当前找个办法来解决
then you better find a way to do it in the here and now.
就像是我前妻跟一个他妈的园丁
It's like my ex-wife used to say before she
跑去厄瓜多尔之前总爱说的
ran off to Ecuador with the fucking gardener.
你得活在当下 伙计
You gotta live in the moment, man.
这杯算我请
This one's on the house.
谢了
Thanks.
这是什么？
What is it?
黄油乳头
A buttery nipple.
加油
Come on!
啊 快点
Uh! Hurry!
怎么了？
What's wrong?
抱歉 我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't.
我就是做不到
I just can't.
来吧
Come on.
别
Please.
维基 我现在想独自静静
Vicky, I need to be alone right now.
你想谈谈吗？
Do you want to talk about it?
不
No.
噢 好吧
Oh, okay.
无所谓
That's fine.
我真是会挑人 哈？
I really know how to pick 'em, huh?
我不是不行
It's nothing personal.
什么？
What?
你是… 你是同志吗？
Are you… Are you gay?
我能把你介绍给我的朋友布伦丹
I could introduce you to my friend Brendan.
他也是个同志 也许你们能在一块儿
He's gay, too. Maybe you guys could hang out!
这样吧 我肯定会给你他的号码
Well, I'll be sure to give you his number,
然后你们能去 你知道 做些男人的事儿
and you can go, you know, do man things.
听起来不错吧？
Sound good?
丽贝卡…
Rebecca…
罗尼…
Lonnie…
嘿 利兹 我是塞姆
Hey, Liz. It's Sam.
我改变主意了
I changed my mind.
我会帮你的
I'll help you out.
你有五分钟
You got five minutes.
你好
Hello.
嘿 罗尼
Hey, Lonnie.
塞姆瑞德 记得我吗？
Sam Reide. Remember me?
南庞蒂克高中
South Pontiac High.
南庞蒂克灰熊队
South Pontiac Grizzly Bears.
我来这儿帮你的
I'm here to help you.
听着 罗尼 我知道你没有杀害丽贝卡布朗
Look, Lonnie. I know you didn't kill Rebecca Brown.
上帝啊 罗尼 说话啊
Jesus, Lonnie. Say something.
你来这儿干嘛？
Why are you here?
我刚说过
I just told you.
你来这儿嘲笑我？
You here to laugh at me?
不是 听着 罗尼
No, look, Lonnie.
我知道你爱着丽贝卡
I know you loved Rebecca.
我知道她爱你
I know she loved you.
我知道怎么回事
I know what was going on.
她写了关于你的一切 就在这儿
She wrote all about it, right here.
你想干嘛？
What are you trying to do?
我们能重新开庭
We can get a new trial.
听着 罗尼 我觉得你没听我说
Look, Lonnie. I don't think you heard me.
这是个新的证据
This is new evidence.
警察不想重审这个案子
The police don't want to reopen the case,
可我们能申请缓刑
but we can request a stay of execution.
新的证据 重新开庭
New evidence. New trial.
- 你会被释放的 - 不
- You'll be exonerated. - No.
你听懂了没？
Do you understand?
- 我会把这带给你的律师 - 不行
- I'm sending this to your lawyer. - No.
罗尼你能不能就看看这日记
Lonnie, would you just look at the diary!
是你
It was you.
你杀了她
You killed her.
我在这儿被关了十年
And I've been locked in here for 10 years!
而你却逍遥法外
And you've been free!
你不能来这儿这样对我
You can't come in here and do this to me!
你不能现在来装好人
You can't pretend to be the good guy now!
这不公平
It's not fair!
是你做的 塞姆
You did it, Sam!
你该在这儿
You should be in here!
走吧 是你做的 塞姆
Let's go. You did it, Sam!
这不公平
It's not fair!
It's not fair.
我永远也习惯不了这种冷
I'll never get used to this cold.
那么今晚的主题是什么？
So what's on the menu tonight?
谋杀？强奸？还是汽车肇事？
Homicide? Rape? Vehicular manslaughter?
丽贝卡布朗
Rebecca Brown.
塞姆 你这是在干嘛？
Sam, what are you doing?
没事的 珍娜
It's okay, Jenna.
把号码给我就行
Just give me the numbers.
你在违反规则
You're breaking the rules.
我打破的是我的规则
They're my rules to break.
你救不了她的 塞姆
You can't save her, Sam.
我能在这里通过安全的方式进行
I can do this here, the safe way,
或者在家里 独自承担风险
or I can do it at home by myself and risk everything.
- 塞姆… - 不论哪种方式 我都会做
- Sam… - Either way, I'm gonna do it.
这不是个好主意
This is a bad idea.
给我号码
The numbers.
1998年 6月6日
June 6th, 1998.
凶杀案发生于上午12：40左右
Murder happened approximately 12:40 a.m.
那是星期六
on a Saturday.
是谁在那边？
Who's in there?
我有枪的
I have a fucking gun.
利兹 利兹 是我
Liz. Liz. It's me.
塞姆？
Sam?
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
不 不 不 真酷
No, no, no. It's cool.
不 周末我父母不在镇里
No. My parents are out of town this weekend.
- 不 不是… 来嘛 - 我有些葡萄酒…
- No, no… - Come on. I got some wine coolers…
- 贝基叫它「泼妇酒」 - 关上门…
- Becky calls it "bitch beer." - Lock the doors…
- 来点泼妇酒吗？- 回到车上去
- You want some bitch beer? - Get back in the car!
- 我不会回车上的… - 听着
- I'm not getting back in my car… - Listen.
你很危险 我是认真的 明白吗？
You're in danger. This is serious, okay?
到车里去
Get in the car.
成吗？
Okay?
快点
Come on.
关上车门
Keep the doors locked.
如果你看到什么 就按喇叭
If you see anything, honk your horn.
明白吗？
Okay?
丽贝卡？
Rebecca?
伊丽莎白 伊丽莎白
Elizabeth! Elizabeth!
嘿 兄弟 没事吧？
Hey, man. You okay?
你是谁？
Who are you?
帕克 不记得了？
Paco. You know?
我租了你的沙发
I rent your couch.
我出租了我的沙发？
I rent out my couch?
是缺钱了 白痴
It's the recession, pendejo.
- 我的汽车钥匙在哪？- 汽车钥匙？
- Where are my car keys? - Car keys?
你没有汽车啊
You don't have a car.
不要再来这里了
You gotta stop showing up here.
我需要关于丽贝卡布朗谋杀案的档案
I need the case file on the Rebecca Brown murder.
这是最后一次
This is the last time.
这家伙是谁？
So who's this guy?
他是10年前布朗谋杀案的一名嫌疑人
He was a suspect in the Brown murder 10 years ago.
不过现在他无法摆脱这案子的困扰
But now he's obsessed with the case.
什么 你觉得他能成我们的人？
What, do you think he might be our guy?
我觉得他只是个失落的灵魂
I think he's just a lost soul.
嘿 给他一些其它的吧
Hey, let's show him the others.
什么？
What?
如果他是杀人犯 我们会知道的
If he's the killer, we'll know.
报纸上称这个家伙为「切割手」
Paper's calling our guy the "Pontiac Killer."
喜欢这个名字吗？
You like that name?
他有什么花样？
What's his pattern?
尾随年轻女子 然后尸解她们
He tracks young women, and cuts them apart.
目前已知的 有八位受害者
Eight victims so far, that we know of.
大约每年一位
It's about one a year.
有什么线索吗？
Any leads?
你问题可真多 兄弟
You got a lot of questions, buddy.
是吗 然而…
Yeah, well…
你们似乎没有任何答案
You don't seem to have any answers.
喂？
Hello?
珍娜 嘿
Jenna. Hey.
塞姆
Sam.
你在哪呀？没事吧？
Where have you been? You okay?
我来接你
I've been trying to reach you.
呃 不用了 我没事 我很好
Uh, no. I'm fine. I'm fine.
我只是… 需要些帮助
I just… I need some help.
怎么了？缺钱了？
What's wrong? You need money?
不 不是…
No. No…
听着
Listen.
珍娜 你还记得罗尼弗莱内斯吗？
Jenna, do you remember Lonnie Flennons?
当然记得 每当我看到他无趣的生意
Of course I do, every time I see his stupid commercials.
弗莱内斯和莫诺翰 律师事务所
Flennons and Monohan, Attorneys at Law.
- 他是名律师？- 塞姆
- He's a lawyer? - Sam.
你最好别去烦罗尼
You need to leave Lonnie alone.
你在说些什么？
What are you talking about?
你又穿越时空了？
Did you jump again?
你确实这么做了 是吧？我想我们已经说过这些了
You did, didn't you? I thought we talked about this.
塞姆 我现在替你担心…
Sam, I'm worried about you…
呃 珍娜…
Uh, Jenna…
不用担心 行吗？
Don't worry about it, okay?
我稍后就来 然后将一切解释清楚
I'll be by later, and I'll explain everything.
好的…
Okay…
罗尼弗莱内斯在哪间办公室？
Which office is Lonnie Flennons'?
您有预约吗？
Do you have an appointment?
- 是这间吗？- 先生 你不能进去
- Is it this one? - Sir, you can't go in there.
先生 先生 你不能进去
Sir! Sir! You can't go in there!
你不能进去 先生
You can't go in there! Sir!
我得和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
抱歉 我告诉过他不能进来…
I'm sorry. I told him he couldn't come in…
没关系 我们是老朋友
It's okay. We're old friends.
谋杀案那晚你在哪？
Where were you the night of the murders?
你指的是什么？
What is this?
呵？这是我们的周年纪念日吗？
Huh? Is this our anniversary?
你来这里 然后每五年问我同一个问题？
You come in here, and you ask me the same question every five years?
我想知道你当时在哪
I want to know where you were.
你仍然认为我有嫌疑？
You still think I was involved?
啊 别这样
Aw, come on.
呵？瞧 所有人都知道贝基和伊丽莎白
Huh? Look, everybody knows Becky and Elizabeth
是切割手的受害者
were victims of the Pontiac Killer.
上帝啊 你去哪了 过着原始人的生活呢？
Jesus. Where you been, living under a rock?
告诉我你当时在哪
Tell me where you were!
她们被杀的那晚
The night they were killed,
我本想在房子边停车
I thought of stopping by the house.
丽贝卡打电话给我说她父母不在镇里
Rebecca called me and told me her parents were out of town.
我看到你和伊丽莎白在外面聊天
I saw you and Elizabeth talking outside.
我觉得我该回避
I thought I should steer clear.
她还没告诉你 我和她之间的事
She hadn't told you about us.
然后我回家了 这就是全部
I went home, and that was that.
我是完全清白的
I was cleared of all charges.
好啊 那我们就说说
Yeah. Let's just say
你的名字已被加回到嫌疑犯名单中了
your name's been added back to the suspect pool.
我完全赞同反对歧视
I'm all for antidiscrimination.
该死的是 我以此为生
Hell, I made my living at it.
别这样 塞姆
Come on, Sam.
罗尼 到底发生了什么？
Lonnie, what happened?
别再说了
Stop it.
这是什么时候发生的？
When did this happen?
你不记得了吗？
You don't remember?
我有时健忘
I forget things sometimes.
我被搞糊涂了 弄得一团糟
I get confused. I get mixed up.
「嘿 罗尼 我们聚聚吧
"Hey, Lonnie, let's get together.
喝上几杯「
Let's have a drink."
然后1杯变成了20杯
And then one drink turns into 20 drinks,
然后那天晚上你叫了辆计程车
and then you get a cab that night.
多久以前的事情？
How long ago was this?
2003年 6月6日
June 6th, 2003.
那之后五年…
It was five years after the…
上帝啊
God.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
真的很抱歉
知道吗 很长一段时间里 我深信
You know, for the longest time, I was convinced
是你杀了布朗姐妹
you killed the Brown sisters.
- 我？- 是啊
- Me? - Yeah.
丽贝卡常担心你会发现我和她的事情
Rebecca was always afraid you'd find out about us.
她总以为你在监视她
She always thought you were watching her.
比如 在转角处监视 窥探
You know, waiting around the corner, spying.
是你杀了她们吗 塞姆？
Did you kill them, Sam?
不是
No.
我没有
I didn't.
我花了几年教你如何使用能力
I spent years teaching you to use your gift,
而现在你已经创造了切割手
and now you've created the Pontiac Killer.
该死 兄弟
Shit, man.
- 尽管如此 我能弥补 - 不错
- I can fix it, though. - Good.
如果我比这个时间早一小时回到
If I just jump back to the night Rebecca and Elizabeth were killed,
丽贝卡和伊丽莎白被谋杀的那晚
except an hour earlier this time.
得了 那不会有用的
Well, that's not going to work.
我得告诉你
I'll tell you,
回到一个你已经回到过的时间
you go back to a time that you've already jumped,
那会把你脑子烧坏的
you're going to end up frying your brain.
嘿 嘿 嘿 别闻那个
Hey, hey, hey, don't sniff that.
除非你真的想 接下来一个小时都瘫痪在地上
Unless you really want to lie on the floor here paralyzed for the next hour.
那边的… 是布蓉达嘎
That right there… that's Burundanga.
它是恶魔的呼吸
It's the Devil's Breath.
那你种这些是因为…
And you grow this because…
这里是该死的底特律 兄弟
It's fucking Detroit, man.
在我窗子下放些这个
Put a few of those under my window.
比买防盗警铃便宜多了
Cheaper than buying a burglar alarm.
好吧 那如果我回到凶杀案四小时前会怎样？
Okay, so what if I go back four hours before the murders?
没用的
Won't work.
德伯格 我已经创造了一个连环杀手
Goldburg, I've created a serial killer.
我得阻止他
I have to stop him.
好啊 这里有你能做的
Okay. Here's what you can do.
你说有八宗谋杀案 是吗？
You said there's eight murders, right?
那好 回到另外一个那时候 第三个受害者
Okay. So go back to the next one, victim number three.
- 等等 那伊丽莎白怎么办？- 不 不 不 停 停
- Well, wait. What about Elizabeth? - No, no, no. Stop. Stop.
你得遵守规则
You got to stick to the rules.
遵守规则
Stick to the rules.
只看就好 只能看
Just observe. Observe.
就像你常做的那样
Like you always do.
这个第三号受害者…
This victim number three…
不是你认识的人 没错吧？
it's nobody you know, right?
没错
Right.
好的
Good.
然后你记住杀手的身份
Then you ID the killer.
我是说 确定无疑后
I mean, beyond the shadow of a frickin' doubt.
去找警察
Then you go to the police,
给他们留个言 把他告发
drop them a note, turn him in.
剩下的只有一件事情
And then there's just one more thing.
你将会深深地…
You'll be altering…
改变整件事情
the course of events significantly.
那么当你回来时…
So when you get back…
就是说 如果它成功了
That is, if it worked.
当你回来…
When you come back…
不了 谢谢
No, thank you.
妈的 我想不起来了 刚才我们说到哪了？
Shit, I lost my train of thought. What were we talking about?
没关系 德伯格 我想我明白了
It's okay, Goldburg. I think I got it.
我回来的时候 那个杀人狂魔已经在监狱里了
I come back, the serial killer's behind bars.
杀人狂魔 对 就是这样
Serial killer. That's right. Yeah. That's it.
关进监狱 对 很不错
Behind the bars. Yeah. That's good.
谢谢 德伯格 你真棒
Thanks, Goldburg. You're brilliant.
真棒 是 好吧
Brilliant. Yeah, okay.
我以为你会说「真性感」
Thought you were going to say "sexy."
不错 没问题
That's okay. No problem.
还是会度过非常美好的一天
Still going to have a good day.
嘿 等下 别忘了
Hey, wait. Don't forget.
珍娜订了地方
Jenna put in an order.
我今天不能过去了
I can't get over there today.
你能来太好了
Nice of you to show up.
嗯 收拾好了？
Mmm. Cleaned up?
没 我还没
No I didn't.
这是什么？
What's this?
三号受害者 阿妮塔巴恩斯
Victim number three, Anita Barnes.
塞姆 别
Sam, no.
没事的 我又不认识她
It's okay. I don't know her.
这只是和平常一样的 我回去查明了罪犯的身份
This is business as usual. I pop back and ID the perp.
你在开玩笑吧
You got to be kidding me.
我不会让你这么做的
I'm not letting you do this.
每一次你回去 都会有人死
Every time you go back, people die.
你难道还不明白吗？
Can't you learn that?
警察没有任何计划
Police don't have any leads.
我是唯一能阻止他的人
I'm the only one who can stop him.
想想吧 塞姆 还要把事情搞到多糟？
Think this through, Sam. How bad does it have to get?
我能弥补的
I can fix this.
这一次我不会再帮你了
I'm not helping you this time.
塞姆…
Sam…
哦 德伯格跟你问好
Oh, Goldburg says hi.
好吧 三号受害者
Okay, victim number three.
阿妮塔巴恩斯
Anita Barnes.
2000年九月五号
September 5th, 2000.
米勒顿街5133号
5133 Millerton Street.
米勒顿5133号
5133 Millerton.
阿妮塔巴恩斯 三号受害人
Anita Barnes, victim number three.
等着瞧吧 等着瞧
Just watch. Just watch.
等着瞧
Just watch.
天哪
Jesus.
她真是我的心灵伴侣
She's my soul mate.
我的天
God.
起来 他妈的给我起来 婊子
Get up! Get the fuck up, bitch!
没人能听见你
Nobody's going to hear you!
不
No!
他妈的闭嘴 我发誓我他妈会杀了你
Shut the fuck up! I swear I will fucking kill you!
他妈的给我闭嘴
Shut the fuck up!
别看我 别看我 别看我
Don't look at me! Don't look at me! Don't look at me.
不
No!
听见我说的没有？听见了吗？你他妈的听见我说的没有？
You hear me? Do you hear me? Do you fucking hear me?
- 说「是的 我听见了 是 我听见了」 - 是 是
- Say, "Yes, I hear you. Yes, I hear you." - Yes! Yes!
我要把你的脖子弄断
I will fucking snap your neck!
转过来…
Turn…
闭嘴 闭嘴
Shut up! Shut up!
闭嘴 闭嘴 听见了吗？
Shut up! Shut up! You hear me?
他妈的闭嘴 打开…
Shut the fuck up! Open…
哦 妈的 我不能
Oh, shit! I can't.
我不能
I can't.
我做不到
I can't do this.
- 对不起 - 什么？
- I'm sorry. - What?
我连句完整的话都说不了
I didn't even say the safe word.
- 我做不到 - 但是你做的好极了
- I can't do this. - But you were doing great!
我知道 只是…
I know. It's just…
你那么喊叫的时候我根本硬不起来
I can't get hard when you're screaming and crying like that.
- 真烦人 我只是… - 你知道我很享受这个
- It's upsetting. I just… - You know I'm enjoying this!
我知道 只是…
I know. It's just…
斯摩说如果我们把这当作游戏 我们就会乐在其中
Cosmo said if we treat this like a game, we can have fun with this.
我知道斯摩说的 怎么了？
I know what Cosmo says, okay?
我做不到 我是说 我们得想想办法了
I can't do it. I mean, we need to do something.
- 否则 我们怎么让它变的有趣呢… - 我知道
- Otherwise, how are we going to spice… - I know.
你一直都在提醒我 不是吗？但是这个太他妈奇怪了
You remind me all the time, okay? But this shit is weird.
- 感觉不对 - 为什么？
- It feels wrong. - Why?
- 因为我乐在其中 - 但是我也乐在其中啊
- Because I'm enjoying it. - But I'm enjoying it, too.
我不应该享受强奸你的过程啊 真是疯了
I shouldn't enjoy raping you. That's crazy.
你只是把这想的太严重了
You're completely overanalyzing this.
好吧 我知道 每次我一想到这个 我就硬不起来
Okay, I know. Every time I start thinking, I can't get hard.
这就 让我的情绪很糟
It's, like, fucking up my vibe.
现在我的思维已经跑了一百万米…
And now my mind's racing a million mi…
我只是…
I just…
知道吗？
You know what?
别担心 这没什么
Don't worry. It's okay.
去找调解人吧
Just go get the accommodator.
- 这是什么？- 听我解释
- What the fuck? - I can explain this.
你在衣橱里干什么呢 你这个疯子？
What are you doing in the closet, you pervert?
- 我是疯子？- 对 你…
- I'm the pervert? - Yes, you…
马上离开这 混蛋 否则我要叫警察了
I want you out of here, pendejo, or I'll call the cops.
你他妈的在说什么呢？
What the fuck you talking about, man?
你租了我的沙发 你得给我钱
You rent my couch, you pay me.
你如果不给钱 就去找其它的地方睡觉 混蛋
You don't pay me, you find somewhere else to sleep, pendejo.
好的 伙计 我会走的
Fine, man. I'll be out of here.
别担心
Don't worry.
我下周或上上周之前就会走的
I'll be out of here next week or the week before last.
两天前 你他妈的
Two days ago. Fuck you.
德伯格 开门
Goldburg, open up.
是我 塞姆
It's me, Sam.
德伯格 开门
Goldburg, open the door!
德伯格 你在里面吗？
Goldburg, you in there?
（失踪者：德伯格）
好吧 阿妮塔巴恩斯
Okay. Anita Barnes.
真有趣
Funny.
阿妮塔
Anita!
不好意思
Excuse me.
对不起 别害怕 好吗？
I'm sorry. Don't be scared, okay?
- 别碰我 - 我只想问你几个问题
- Get away from me. - I just need to ask you a few questions.
我有一个你的法院制止令
I have a restraining order against you.
- 什么？- 你是那个躲在衣柜里的疯子
- What? - You're that perv from the closet!
等下 不 听着 听我解释 好吗？
Wait. No, listen. I can explain that, okay?
我只是想保护你 我觉得我成功了
I was trying to protect you, and I think it worked.
但是我需要知道你为什么还活着
But I need to figure out why you're still alive.
救命 叫警察
Somebody please help! Call the cops!
- 听着 - 救命
- Listen! - Please help me!
你认识一个叫罗尼弗莱内斯的人吗？
Have you ever known somebody named Lonnie Flennons?
- 救命 - 别 别 别
- Please help! - No, no, no!
没事的 我认识她
It's okay. I know her.
妈的 妈的
Shit! Shit!
塞姆 你还好吗？
Sam, are you okay?
是的 我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
不 你不好 看看你吧
No, you're not. Look at you.
- 只是点辣椒粉喷雾 我很好 - 怎么了？
- Just pepper spray. I'm fine. - What happened?
没什么
Nothing.
- 我看看 - 我没事
- Let me see. - I'm fine!
阿妮塔巴恩斯这个名字 对你而言有什么意义吗？
Does the name Anita Barnes mean anything to you?
你单独行动了
You jumped without me.
塞姆 你知道这有多危险吗？
Sam, do you know how dangerous that is?
- 你会被淹死 你的大脑会被压扁 - 我不能只是…
- You could drown. Your brain could boil. - I can't just…
我现在不想听你的长篇大论 珍娜
I don't need a lecture from you right now, Jenna.
我想知道的是…
What I need to know…
我想知道的是为什么 阿妮塔巴恩斯还活着
What I need to figure out is why Anita Barnes is still alive.
是的 我单独行动了
I jumped. I did.
我回去了 以为我能看见她被谋杀
I went back, and I was supposed to witness her murder.
切割手的第三个受害人
She was victim number three of the Pontiac Killer.
- 现在我回来了 只是… - 什么？
- Now I come back, and it's just… - What?
现在我不知道了 就像一堆转来转去的迷题一样
Now I don't know. It's like all the pieces of the puzzle just shifted around.
唯一能解释这些的人是德伯格
The only person who could explain it to me is Goldburg,
现在他失踪了
and now he's disappeared.
是的 太合时宜了
Yeah, conveniently.
- 你说那话是什么意思？- 塞姆 他会成为
- What does that mean? - Sam, he was going to
把你和谋杀案联系在一起的线索
turn in evidence linking you to the murders.
如果你没有从过去转送的那么快的话 你会明白的
If you hadn't fast forwarded through your past, you'd know that.
你说什么呢？
What are you talking about?
塞姆 你相信我 不是吗？
Sam, you trust me, don't you?
我是说 如果你有任何理由做这件事的话
I mean, if you're doing this for any reason,
我不会阻止你的
I'd never turn you in.
这很荒谬
This is ridiculous.
塞姆 布朗杀人案的那个晚上 我掩护了你
Sam, the night of the Brown murders, I covered for you.
我知道你没在家
I know you weren't at home.
你知道我在哪 我想救他们
You know where I was! I tried to save them!
塞姆 你不知道两周前发生了什么
Sam, you don't know what happened two weeks ago.
是 我知道我没杀任何人
Yeah, I know I didn't kill anybody.
好吧 也许不是现在 但是…
Okay. Maybe not now, but…
如果时空穿越把你弄疯了怎么办
what if with the jumping you go crazy,
在未来的某一天…
and sometime in the future…
塞姆 你从来就不提这个
Sam, you don't talk about it.
你什么都不说 把它控制的严严实实
You don't talk about anything. You just bottle it all up.
你甚至从没提过着火 的时候到底发生了什么
We've never even talked about what happened in the fire.
是你… 是你放的火吗？
Did you… Did you start the fire?
我救了你 珍娜
I saved your life, Jenna.
我看见你死了
I saw you die.
我去了你的葬礼 他妈的
I went to your funeral, for fuck's sake.
我不想伤害别人 珍娜
I don't want to hurt people, Jenna.
我没有那么做 我在帮助别人
I don't do that. I help people.
你看见了？我 我帮助… 我弥补了那些事情
You see? I-I help… I fix things.
这就是我做的 这就是我做过的 我回到过去 弥补那些事情
It's what I do. That's what I did! I went back, and I fixed it.
是我弥补了它 珍娜
I fixed it, Jenna!
这就是为什么你在这 我可以弥补
That's why you're here, because I fix things!
你知道的 但是有的时候你并不能弥补一切
You know, but sometimes you can't fix everything.
有时事情就是会变得他妈的一团糟 珍娜
Sometimes things are just fucked, Jenna!
而且… 而且现在 事情就已经有点变糟了
And… And right now, things are kind of fucked!
所以 我…
So, I…
我在试着… 我在试着…
I'm try… I'm try…
- 我在试着弥补 但是… - 塞姆
- I'm trying to fix it, but it… - Sam.
我只是不知道为什么
I just don't know why.
我太笨了或者我太… 我太软弱了
I'm too stupid or I'm too… I'm too weak!
- 它… 它只是… - 塞姆 塞姆
- It's… I… It's just… - Sam. Sam.
会没事的
It's going to be okay.
是时空穿越
It's the jumping.
就让警察履行一次他们的职责吧
Just let the police do their job for once.
塞姆
Sam.
向我保证你再也不会做时空穿越了
Promise me you're not going to jump anymore.
向我保证
Promise.
我会弥补的 珍娜
I can fix it, Jenna.
不
No.
噢 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
- 再见 大伙儿 - 晚安 维基
- Bye, guys. - Night, Vicki.
晚点见
See you later.
你有没想过假如你能 回到过去改变一件事
You ever wonder how your life would be different
你的人生会有怎样的变化？
if you could go back and change one thing?
有 每个人都这么想过
Yeah. Everyone thinks about that.
再见
Bye.
嘿 想听个笑话吗？
Hey, want to hear a joke?
好啊
Sure.
把贵妃鸡和黄牛混起来
What do you get when you mix a brown chicken
会得到什么？
and a brown cow?
我不知道 会得到什么？
I don't know. What do you get?
贵妃鸡 黄牛
Brown chicken, brown cow
很有趣 是吧？
It's funny, right?
嘿 维基 你晚点想不想过来？
Hey, Vicki, you want to come over later?
谢谢你的邀请 但我要回我男人那
Thanks for the offer, but I got to get home to my man.
好吧
Right.
嗯
Yeah.
也许下辈子吧
Maybe in another life.
嗯 下辈子
Yeah. In another life.
谢谢你
Thank you.
- 再见 塞姆 - 再见
- Bye, Sam. - Bye.
贵妃鸡 黄牛
Brown chicken, brown cow
已经打烊了
We're closed!
有人吗？
Is there anyone in here?
也许预约取消了
Guess the engagement's off.
你找到的就只有这些吗？
Is that all you found?
法医修复了一具烧焦的尸体
Forensics recovered a charred body
数据显示其符合东车厂的报告
matching a description at the Eastern body plant.
是她
It's her.
是的 除非是最后一位客人的
Yep. Unless it was the last customer.
酱汁不错
Good sauce.
我再问一次
Let's go over it again.
你昨晚几点离开酒吧？
What time did you leave the bar last night?
我不知道 我醉了
I don't know. I was drunk.
你室友说你大概三点到
Your roommate says you got in about 3.
谋杀案在凌晨2：30发生
The murders took place at 2:30 a.m.
从你那到酒吧要走多久路？
How long is the walk from the bar to your place?
半个小时吧？
About half an hour?
你真觉得我是那个切割手吗？
You really think I'm the Pontiac Killer?
你是布朗姐妹谋杀案的嫌疑人
You were a person of interest in the Brown murders,
但你妹妹为你提供了不在场证明
but you got off on your sister's alibi.
你在罗尼弗莱内斯死前一天去找过他
You showed up at Lonnie Flennons' the day before he dies.
然后你刚好又在那天晚上出现在酒吧
And now you just happen to be at the bar the night
维基最有一次剪指甲了
Vicki gets her last manicure.
别这样 格伦 别这么说她
Come on, Glenn. Don't talk about her like that.
别跟猪似的
Don't be a pig.
也许他们需要隐私
Guess they need their privacy.
我跟你说怎么着
Now I'm going to tell you how it's going to happen.
你会后悔的
You're going to confess.
你会承认自己是疯子的
You're going to plead insanity.
我要证明给你看你他妈的就是个人渣
I'm going to testify myself to what a crazy motherfucker you are.
因为如果你继续胡说八道
Because if you keep giving me this tired-ass song and dance
以为自己能阻止切割手
about trying to stop the Pontiac Killer,
我保证你会和那些神经病关在一起
I'll make sure you're locked up in county with them big old boys.
现在你觉得爽了吧？
Now don't it just make your asshole pucker?
格伦
Glenn.
他妹妹来了 带了一个律师
The sister's here. She's got a lawyer.
- 所以呢？- 她请来了博斯维奇
- So? - She's got Boswich.
天哪
Jesus.
你有足够证据定罪吗？
Have you got enough for a conviction?
看情况
It's all circumstantial.
现在怎么办？
Now what?
去停尸间
Go back to the auto body plant.
扫瞄指纹
Sweep for fingerprints.
看看能发现些什么
See what else you can find.
- 我们已经去过了 - 再认真找找
- We were already there. - Then look harder.
我们要拿这个神经病怎么办？
What are we going to do about psychic boy?
你觉得呢？
What do you think?
- 我们只能让他走了 - 跟踪他
- We have to let him walk. - Put a tail on him.
今年老虎队看起来状态不错
The Tigers are looking good this year.
好了 他们放他出来了
All right. They're letting him out.
格伦警官 我们有麻烦了
Detective Glenn, we got a problem.
- 很抱歉 - 我也很抱歉
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry, too.
- 你没事吧？- 没事
- You okay? - Yeah.
晚上过得怎么样？
How was your night?
东车厂
Eastern body plant.
警察在那找到切割手的受害人
This is where the police found the Pontiac Killer's victims.
2004年9月19号 2004年9月19号
September 19, 2004. September 19, 2004.
你想怎样？
What do you want?
我要拉屎 混蛋
I got to take a shit, pendejo.
五分钟
Five minutes.
我烦死你那他妈的「五分钟」了
I'm tired of your fucking "five minutes."
我知道混蛋是什么意思
And I know what pendejo means.
他妈的滚出去
Get the fuck out!
不付租金就给我滚
You don't pay rent, you leave.
我毫不在乎
I don't give a shit.
2004年9月19号
September 19, 2004.
在警察发现受害人的旧车厂
The old auto body plant where the police find the victims.
他们查清楚了 切割手什么时候回来？
They figured it out. When did the Pontiac Killer start coming here?
为什么他要折磨受害人？
Why did he torture his victims?
我一定要找到他
I got to find him.
我要看着他的脸 盯着他的眼睛
I want to see his face, look into his eyes.
盯着他的眼睛
Look into his eyes.
我要看见他的脸 盯着他的眼睛
I want to see his face, look into his eyes.
嘿
Hey.
在中午前不要睡觉
Don't sleep until noon today.
珍娜？
Jenna?
我把机密文件留在了咖啡桌上
I'm leaving the classifieds on the coffee table.
也许你能看看上面有没有适合你的工作
Maybe you can look and see if there's a job in there for you.
你要去哪？
Where you going?
工作 今天是周一
Work. It's Monday.
噢 那好吧
Oh, that's right.
噢 嗯 我六点回来
Oh, uh, I'll be back at 6.
- 你来做饭 是吗？- 我做饭？
- You're going to cook dinner, right? - I make dinner?
嗯 当然
Hell, yeah.
还有你说过你会打扫卫生的
And you said you were going to clean up.
你的计划听起来有些恐怖
This little project of yours is starting to look kind of scary.
切割手 八个受害人 都是女的
The Pontiac Killer. Eight victims, all women.
不 他杀了罗尼弗莱内斯 七个受害人
No, he killed Lonnie Flennons. Seven victims.
七个女人 一个男人
Seven women, one man.
他把尸体藏起来 他会放到哪里去？
He hides their bodies. Where does he take them?
东车厂 他为什么要放到那里？
The Eastern body plant. Why does he take them there?
某些受害人有被虐待的痕迹 其他的是立即死亡
Some victims have signs of torture, others killed immediately.
他的计划是什么？他怎么会没别人发现？
What's his pattern? How does he get out undetected?
邻居们都没见怪声 他一定是晚上去的… 晚上
Neighbors never hear him. He must go at night… at night.
啊 他是住在那吗？他是在附近工作吗？
Ah, does he live there? Does he work nearby?
我一定要找到他 我要回去 我要回去
I've got to find him. I've got to go back. I've got to go back.
这些女人有什么共同之处？
What did these women all have in common?
有什么… 他们之间有什么联系？
What's the… What's the connection?
这家伙要干嘛 嗯？
What's this guy about, huh?
噢 伙计
Oh, man.
阿妮塔巴恩斯 她快把我烦死了
Anita Barnes. That's the one that's killing me.
阿妮塔巴恩斯
Anita Barnes.
想想看 那有个…
Let's see. There was…
别动 王八蛋 别动 他妈的别动
Freeze, motherfucker! Not a move! Not a fucking move!
- 跪下 - 他妈的给我跪下
- On your knees! - On your fucking knees!
趴下 他妈的趴下 脸朝下 快点
Move down! Get the fuck down! Face down! Come on!
- 给他一巴掌 - 把手放到背后
- Cuff him. - Hands behind your back!
- 叫他们进来 - 好的 叫进来
- Call them up. - All right. Call it in.
啊
Ouch.
你真的都计划好了一切
You really had this all mapped out.
你看
Look at that.
也许你是个神经病 但这一切都是你造成的
You may be a nut job, but you sure made this
一个惊天大案
a slam-dunk case for us.
你的女朋友 贝基 给你戴绿帽
I mean, your girlfriend, Becky, cheats on you,
所以你就杀了他
so you kill her.
然后你杀了她姐姐 因为…
Then you kill her sister because…
我不知道… 杀一送一？
I don't know… Bonus points?
你的朋友 德伯格 准备指证你
Your pal Goldburg was going to testify against you.
但他突然消失了
Then he disappears.
然后你杀了罗尼弗莱内斯 我不知道
And then you kill Lonnie Flennons. I don't know.
- 不 不 不是的 - 什么？
- No, no. No. - What?
罗尼 将要被执行死刑 我必须回去
Lonnie was going to be executed. I had to go back.
你他妈的到底在说什么？最后的受害者
What the fuck you talking about? The next victim.
是谁？
Which one?
- 阿妮塔巴恩斯 - 谁？
- Anita Barnes. - Who?
阿妮塔巴恩斯 阿妮塔巴恩斯
Anita Barnes. Anita Barnes.
是我… 是他…
Did I… Did he…
- 他杀了阿妮塔巴恩斯吗？- 我不知道 你告诉我啊
- Did he kill Anita Barnes? - I don't know. You tell me.
- 我杀了阿妮塔巴恩斯吗？- 不知道 你告诉我
- Did I kill Anita Barnes? - No. You tell me.
- 切割手的最后一个受害人什么时候死的？- 听着 混蛋
- When was the last Pontiac victim? - Look, fuck-stick.
现在我问你 你杀了多少个人？
I'm asking the questions here. How many did you kill?
我要打电话
I want my phone call.
5分钟
Five minutes.
你能打电话 然后你打给我？
You get one call, and you call me?
你打算把我开除？
You trying to get me fired?
格伦 我想要离开
Glenn, I got to get out of here.
格伦 我是认真的 知道吗？
Glenn, I'm serious, okay?
那杀手还在外面 我是唯一能阻止他的人
The killer is still out there, and I'm the only one who can stop him.
根据联合警察部门
According to the joint police department,
那切割手就在这里
the Pontiac Killer's right here.
别这样 你相信凶手不是我 格伦
Come on! You don't believe it's me, Glenn!
我惹得麻烦已经够多了 塞姆
I'm in enough trouble as it is, Sam!
好吧 好吧 听着
Okay, okay. Listen.
我不是神经病
I'm not a psychic.
- 我知道 - 我可以穿梭时空
- I knew it. - I time travel.
我可以回到任何地方 我可以观察
I can go back to wherever I was, and I can watch.
这取决于发生什么 我能改变事情
And depending upon what happens, I change things.
通常是偶然的 但有时是有目的的
Usually on accident but sometimes on purpose.
别再打给我
Don't ever call me again.
不 这是事实 格伦 格伦
No, it's true! Glenn! Glenn!
你和你妻子在小加斯科 的16岁生日聚会上相遇
You met your wife at Tiny Gasco's sweet-16 party!
他父亲有一辆塔克货车 还为邻居们请来了乐队
Her dad got a taco cart and a band for the neighborhood!
你妻子走过来向你邀舞
Your wife came up and asked you to dance!
但他跟你说的第一句话是…
But the first thing she ever said to you was…
你是M.C。Hammer吗？
Are you M.C. Hammer?
你怎么知道？
How did you know that?
我回到过去了
I went back.
- 我看到的 - 什么时候？
- I saw it. - When?
几年前 当你第一次问我的时候…
Years ago, when you first started asking me about…
我在挽救这件事啊…
I was saving it…
类似这样的事
for something like this, actually.
那你觉得怎么样？
So what do you say, huh?
你会帮我出去吗？
You'll help me out?
拜托你？
Please?
Hammer？
Hammer?
可以当作是个笔误 文书上的小差错
It's going down as a clerical error. Glitch in the paperwork.
但它只能给你2个多小时
But it'll only buy you a couple more hours.
一旦尼古拉斯发现了 他会把你抓回来
Once Nicholas finds out, he'll bring you in.
他也不会再让我见你了
There's no way he'll let me see you again.
仔细想想
Come to think of it,
我可能会在几个小时内失去工作
I probably won't have a job in a few hours.
你要抓住那个混蛋
You catch that son of a bitch.
珍娜 珍娜
Jenna. Jenna!
珍娜 是我 快点
Jenna, it's me! Come on!
珍娜 开门 再不开我要踢门了
Jenna, open up the door! I'm going to kick it down!
你不能踢开门 你个混蛋
You ain't kicking down shit, motherfucker!
- 现在你他妈的安静点 - 开门
- Now you need to quiet your ass down! - Open up!
你到底怎么回事？
What the hell's wrong with you?
戴维斯小姐 你能开下我妹妹的门吗？
Miss Davis, will you open my sister's door for me?
- 我才不开呢 - 让我进去
- I ain't opening up shit! - Let me into her apartment.
- 我不会… 等等 - 你有他妈的钥匙
- I ain't gonna… Wait! - You got the fucking keys!
- 那你他妈的钥匙呢？- 戴维斯小姐 你他妈的能不能闭嘴？
- Where's your fucking key? - Miss Davis, would you shut the fuck up?
- 你不能抓住我 - 让我进去
- You ain't about to get me! - Let me into this apartment!
不要把手放我身上 混蛋
Don't put your hands on me, motherfucker!
不要逼我砍你
Don't make me have to cut you!
妈的 把你送进监狱都不够
Shit! Too fucking old to go to prison.
你最好进去后尽快出来
You need to get your trifling ass in and out of here as soon as possible!
- 谢谢 - 哦 巴结我
- Thank you. - Oh, kiss my ass!
珍娜？
Jenna?
「最喜爱的顾客」？
"Favorite customer"?
嘿 嘿 嘿 别闻那个
Hey, hey, hey, don't sniff that,
除非接下来几小时你想瘫痪躺在地上
unless you really want to lie on the floor here paralyzed for the next hour.
德伯格
Goldburg!
德伯格 你在里面吗？
Goldburg, you in there?
给我出来
Come on out here!
出来面对我 你这个混…
Come on out and face me, you son of a…
快点
Come on!
德伯格 发生了什么事？
Goldburg. What happened?
嘿 发生了什么事？
Hey, what happened?
德伯格 你会没事的 好吗？
Goldburg, you're going to be all right, okay?
你能站起来吗？你能站起来吗？
Can you stand up? Can you stand up?
我去找人来帮你
I'm going to get you some help.
好吗？我去找人来帮你
Okay? I'm going to get you some help.
我去找人来帮忙
I'm going to get you help.
哦 天哪 哦 妈的
Oh, my God. Oh, fuck.
哦 天哪
Oh, my God.
塞姆my
Sammy.
你在这干什么？
What are you doing here?
那个东西已经夹紧了 来 让我帮你弄开
That thing is spring loaded. Here. Let me get you out of there.
我会弄开的
I'll get it.
来 起来 站起来
Here. Get up. Stand up.
我们得把它从你脚上弄掉
We need to get you out of this thing.
我扶你
I got you.
你脚能出来了吗？
Can you lean out?
珍娜 你在这干什么？
Jenna, what are you doing here?
没事的 塞姆
It's okay, Sam.
塞姆 我会解决所有事的
Sam, I'll fix everything.
我只要回到过去 把夹子移走 你就会没事了
I'll just jump back, and I'll move the trap out of the way. You'll be fine.
- 你也能穿越时空？- 是的
- You can jump? - Yeah.
惊讶吧
Surprise.
为什么你…
Why are you…
你在这干什么？
What are you doing here?
你还没意识到
You don't realize this,
但我已经向你解释过无数次了
but I've explained this to you, like, a zillion times.
真的很受挫
It's really frustrating.
你爱上了那个妓女 塞姆
You fell in love with that whore, Sam.
她却不爱你
She didn't love you.
她对你不忠
She was cheating on you.
什么… 什么妓女？
What… What whore?
丽贝卡布朗
Rebecca Brown.
天哪 塞姆 清醒点
Jesus, Sam. Keep up.
不 不 哦 天哪
No. No. Oh, my God.
我帮你解决了 一切都很顺利
I took care of it, and everything worked out fine.
我甚者报复了伤害你的罗尼弗莱内斯
I even got back at Lonnie Flennons for hurting you.
但丽贝卡布朗的白痴妹妹来找你
But then Rebecca Brown's stupid sister comes over,
然后… 你决定打破规矩 塞姆
and… and you decide to break the rules, Sam.
我告诉过你不要那么做 会有坏事发生
I told you not to do it. I told you it would be bad.
你跟着我回到了过去？
You followed me back?
珍娜 那么… 那么其他那些女孩呢？
Jenna, what about the… What about the other girls?
那么… 你都不认识她们
What about the… You didn't know them.
她们只是陌生人 她们对你做过什么了？
They were strangers. What did they ever do to you?
你没发现吗 塞姆？
Can't you see, Sam?
她们只是陌生人
They were only strangers
是因为我在你认识她们前杀了她们
'cause I stopped them before you met them.
阿妮塔巴恩斯
Anita Barnes.
她是和你一起去芝加哥的妓女
She was the whore you went to Chicago with.
我不能让你离开我 塞姆
I couldn't let you leave me, Sam.
然后是维基
And then Vicki.
你没告诉过我她的事 但还是被我发现了
You kept her a secret from me, too, but I found out.
她不是个好女人 塞姆
She wasn't a lady, Sam.
她们中没一个好女人
None of them were ladies.
珍娜 她们… 她们本该是我爱的女人
Jenna, they… they're the women I would've fallen in love with.
我本该… 我本该有个家庭和新的生活
I would've… I would've had a family, a life.
你没发现我做这一切都是为了你吗？
Don't you see I did it all for you?
你明白的 是不是？
You understand that, don't you?
为什么你要折磨她们？你把她们肢解了
Why did you torture them? You mutilated them!
- 你把她们弄成了碎片 - 我没有折磨她们 是她们折磨我
- You cut them to pieces! - I didn't torture them! They tortured me!
她们中的每一个人
Every single one of them.
那德伯格呢？
What about Goldburg?
他发现了
He was catching on.
我必须让他闭嘴
I had to shut him up.
这真的很像史酷比 是不是？
This is so Scooby-Doo, isn't it?
如果不是那些好管闲事的孩子
I would've gotten away with it
我本该已经逃脱了
if it wasn't for those meddling kids.
你他妈的疯了 珍娜
You're out of your fucking mind, Jenna.
得了吧 塞姆
Come on, Sam.
你知道那不是事实
You know that's not true.
如果不是你总要回去抓我
If you hadn't kept jumping back to catch me,
我可能已经收手了
I could've stopped.
但每次你回去就会有更多的目击者
But every time you went back, there was more witnesses,
就有更多证据需要掩盖
there was more evidence to cover up.
想想挺好笑的
It's funny when you think about it.
你真的创造了个连环杀手
You really did create a serial killer.
从你回到过去救我的那天起
Ever since the day you jumped back and you saved me,
我知道我只为你而活
I knew I'd only live for you.
不 珍娜 珍娜
No, Jenna. Jenna.
塞姆…
Sam…
你有像我爱你那样爱我吗？
do you love me like I love you?
没事的 忘掉其他所有的事
It's okay. Forget about everything else.
这是我们等了一生的重要时刻
This is the moment we've waited for our whole lives.
珍娜 你在干什么？
Jenna! What are you doing?
塞姆 我们不像其他人
Sam, we're not like other people.
他们规矩不适用于我们
Their rules don't apply to us.
不 珍娜 你… 哦 天哪
No, Jenna! You're… Oh, my God.
塞姆 我爱你胜过于一切 塞姆
Sam, I love you more than anything in the whole world, Sam.
- 哦 天哪 - 没事的
- Oh, my God. - It's okay.
只有你和我 就像命中注定的
It's just you and me like it's meant to be.
- 不 不 不 - 没事的
- No. No. No. - It's okay.
没事的 塞姆？
It's okay. Sam?
怎么了？怎么了？怎么回事？
What's wrong? What's wrong? What's going on?
塞姆 你还好吗？
Sam, are you okay?
塞姆 你在穿越时空吗？
Sam, are you jumping?
塞姆 怎么回事？
Sam, what's going on?
告诉我发生了什么事
Tell me what's happening.
塞姆 不要穿越
Sam, don't jump!
你要去哪？塞姆
Where are you going? Sam!
塞姆 不要离开我
Sam, don't you leave me.
塞姆 珍娜在哪？
Sam, where's Jenna?
你照顾好妈妈 我去找她
You go take care of Mom, and I'll get her.
塞姆 帮帮我
Sam, help me!
塞姆 让我出去
Sam, let me out!
让我出去 请你让我出去
Let me out! Please let me out!
你在干什么？塞姆
What are you doing? Sam!
塞姆 住手 你在干什么？
Sam, stop! What are you doing?
- 珍娜 - 塞姆
- Jenna! - Sam!
- 塞姆 - 听我说
- Sam! - Listen to me!
- 你为什么要这么做？- 我是你哥哥 珍娜
- Why are you doing this? - I'm your brother, Jenna.
- 我会一直爱你 - 塞姆 塞姆 你在干什么？
- I'll always love you! - Sam! Sam, what are you doing?
- 没有其他办法 - 塞姆
- There's no other way! - Sam!
塞姆 让我出去
Sam, let me out!
对不起 珍娜
I'm sorry, Jenna!
珍娜在哪 塞姆？
Where's Jenna, Sam?
珍娜在哪？
Where's Jenna?
早上好 呆子脸
Good morning, dork-face.
你睡的好吗？
Did you sleep well?
你一定做梦了
You must've had some kind of dream
因为你打鼾了
because you were snoring away.
- 我们到那了吗？- 是的 珍娜 我们到了
- Are we there yet? - Yes, Jenna, we're there.
珍娜？
Jenna?
什么事 爸爸？
What, Daddy?
走吧
Come on.
汉堡包是怎么来的？
How the burgers coming?
- 他们来了 - 嘿
- Here they are. - Hey.
自己的生日聚会还迟到
Late for your own birthday party.
你好 甜心
Hello, sweetheart.
- 生日快乐 - 嘿
- Happy Birthday. - Hey!
什么？
What?
你想要什么？汉堡包？热狗？还是什么？
What do you want? Burgers? Hot dogs? What?
- 只要是你做的都行 拿上来吧 - 先喝啤酒吧？
- Whatever you're cooking. Throw it on. - Start with a beer?
- 好 嘿 - 生日快乐
- Yeah, sure. Hey! - Happy Birthday.
嘿 珍娜
Hey, Jenna.
- 你好吗？- 我很好
- How are you? - I'm good. I'm good.
嘿
Hey.
你好吗 亲爱的？
How are you, hon?
- 很好 - 我的儿子
- Great. - My son!
你好吗？哦 看到你真好
How are you? Oh, good to see you.
你好 女士
Howdy, ma'am.
我打赌你一定有一两个故事讲 是不是？
I bet you got a story or two for us, don't you?
哦 好兄弟
Oh, man!
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 嘿 生日快乐 - 嘿
- Hey, Happy Birthday. - Hey!
- 哦 天哪 - 见到你真高兴
- Oh, my God! - It's good to see you.
再给贾尼丝一瓶啤酒
Get Janice another beer.